http://www.aie.org.au/privacy-policy

About us
What we do? Office Bearers Constitution and By-Laws AIE Annual Reports & Accounts Contact Us Scholarship and Awards LinkedIn National Board and Executive Women in Energy Committee Nominations & Guidelines
Events
Upcoming Events
The Japan-Australia Energy Dialogue - AIE Members Welcome! Live Stream Events Past Events
Past Events 2017 Past Events 2016 Past Events 2015 Past Events 2014 Past Events 2013 Past Events 2012 Past Events 2011 Past Events 2018 Past Events 2019 Past Events 2020 Presentation Videos Events by other Organisations Conference Proceedings
AIE 2012 CONFERENCE PROCEEDINGS
Membership
Information and Application AIE Youth Scholarship
AIE 2018 Scholarship Winner - Naomi Stringer AIE 2016 Scholarship Winner - Caitlin Trethewy AIE 2015 Scholarship Winner - Megan Aspinall AIE 2014 Scholarship Winner - Carmen Wouters AIE 2013 Scholarship Winner - Joel Baker AIE 2012 Scholarship Winner - Elisabeth Tourneboeuf Corporate Member Directory
Publications
Energy News Journal AIE e-Newsletter
Subscribe to the e-Newsletter 2018 e-Newsletter Archive 2017 e-Newsletter Archive 2016 e-Newsletter Archive 2015 e-Newsletter Archive 2014 e-Newsletter Archive 2013 e-Newsletter Archive 2019 e-Newsletter Archive
2020 e-Newsletter Archive
Branches
Brisbane
Brisbane Information Brisbane Committee & Branch Rules Brisbane Young Energy Professionals Brisbane Events Canberra
Canberra Information Canberra Committee & Branch Rules Canberra Young Energy Professionals Canberra Events Melbourne
Melbourne Information Melbourne Committee & Branch Rules Melbourne Young Energy Professionals Melbourne Events Newcastle
Newcastle Information Newcastle Committee & Branch Rules Newcastle Events Perth
Perth Information Perth Committee & Branch Rules Perth Young Energy Professionals Perth Events Women in Energy - Perth Perth Initiatives South Australia
South Australia Information South Australia Committee & Branch Rules South Australia Young Energy Professionals Hall of fame South Australia Events Sunshine Coast
Sunshine Coast Information Sunshine Coast Committee & Branch Rules Sunshine Coast Events Sydney
Sydney Information Sydney Committee & Branch Rules Sydney Young Energy Professionals Sydney Events Young Energy Professionals
Brisbane Branch Canberra Branch Melbourne Branch
Newcastle Branch Perth Branch South Australia Branch Sydney Branch
Oil & Gas SIG
Interesting and useful articles Links
Members Area
My AIE Live Stream Events Presentations Member Documents Energy News issues Officer Documents
Membership Database Brisbane Committee Canberra Committee Melbourne Committee Newcastle Committee South Australia Committee Sydney Committee Sunshine Coast Committee
Contact Us
Sitemap
Home Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThe Australian Institute of Energy (AIE) understands the importance of protecting the privacy of individuals and is committed to complying with the Privacy Act 1988, and associates National Privacy Principles, to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information collected.Our policy is to respect your privacy and only use any data we collect in the direct service of our members and friends who are interested in our events. We never supply your details to parties outside the AIE or its agents and will always respect your wishes for removal from the email notices or the database. The branch will only grant access to any part of its data as part of service supply if such suppliers have also been bound by a confidentiality undertaking in advance. The Branch committee has adopted internal processes and policies which give effect to honouring our privacy commitments.Specifically:collection – personal information is only collected to ensure members and prospective members are able to be contacted and made aware of services availableuse and disclosure – information will only be used for the benefit of the membership, principally to contact members, and no information will be disclosed to any third party without prior approval.data quality – we aim tol ensure any data collected will be accurate, complete and current, recognising that data accuracy is dependent also on member communication to us.data security – we will protect data from misuse, loss or unauthorised use. Secure pages on our website are protected by a 128-bit SSL certificate.openness – the type of information collected is openly available to anyoneaccess and correction – we encourage personal information to be regularly updated and personal information collected to be available to the individual concernedidentifiers – no Commonwealth or State identifiers are collected or usedanonymity – it is impracticable for members to remain anonymoustransborder data flows – no information will be transferred overseas without prior approvalsensitive information – sensitive information is not collected.Compliance to the National Privacy Principles is supported through procedures documented in the Quality Management System and assured through training of staff and regular review of procedures.Any person wishing to make a complaint regarding the privacy of information should contact the AIE by telephone on 1800 629 945 or email aie@aie.org.au
About Us What we do? Office Bearers Constitution and By-Laws AIE Annual Reports & Accounts Contact Us Scholarship and Awards LinkedIn National Board and Executive Women in Energy Committee Nominations & Guidelines
Events Upcoming Events Live Stream Events Past Events Presentation Videos Events by other Organisations Conference Proceedings
Membership Information and Application AIE Youth Scholarship Corporate Member Directory
Publications Energy News Journal AIE e-Newsletter
Branches Brisbane Canberra Melbourne Newcastle Perth South Australia Sunshine Coast Sydney Young Energy Professionals Oil & Gas SIG
Members Area My AIE Live Stream Events Presentations Member Documents Energy News issues Officer Documents Brisbane Committee Canberra Committee Melbourne Committee Newcastle Committee Update Member Details & Pay Membership
Refund Policy
Privacy
Sitemap
Copyright © 2017 Australian Institute of Energy
AIE
